Indrasena Reddy. G Reatured

Looking for Dynamics365 CRM/Power Apps Technical Consultant



Current Designation: Senior Software Engineer Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 10 Month(s)

Current Company: Bosch Notice Period: Currently Serving Notice Period

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electrical]

Pref. Location: Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: MS Dynamics CRM, Javascript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, JSON, Microsoft Azure, SSIS, Power Bi, Devops, ASP. Net

MVC, Sitecore, Salesforce, Powershell

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

5.8 Years of experience in IT Industry with Analysis, Development, Implementation, and Support in Client-Server & Web-based Architecture across multiple business domains.

3 Years of experience in PowerApps, MS Dynamics CRM 2016, Dynamics365.

2 Years of experience in Sitecore.

Certified in MS Dynamics CRM 2016 Customization and Configuration (MB2-712).

Salesforce CRM Programming: Apex, Visualforce pages,

Experience in integrating Salesforce CRM with CMS Tools (Sitecore and AEM).

Experience in Integrating Dynamic CRM with Word press and Asp.Net websites.

Strong Experience in Configuration, Testing, Training and End User Support.

Provided the MS CRM Training to Subordinates.

Experience in Unified service desk.

Experience in DevOps.

Work Experience

Robert Bosch engineering solutions as Senior Software Engineer

Aug 2018 to Aug 2018

Project Name: Tokyo Electronics (Japan)

Client: Microsoft Location: Hyderabad Role: CI&CD Engineer

Contributes to Project:

- Involving in Form & Fields Customizations.
- Created the Build and release pipelines for Importing and exporting the solutions.
- Monitor the stylecop issues, build report through Devops.
- Created the Custom Agent.
- Prepared the Release Notes for every deployment.
- Involved in CRM development Activities as well.

Project Name ARCESE Client Italy Location Banglore Role **CRM** Developer

Description:

Arcese is a road and intermodal transport to move your business. International air & sea freight for a business without borders. Integrated solutions for the strategic outsourcing of logistics and supply chain management. Contributions to Project:

Involving in Form & Fields customizations

Involving for workflows and plug-in changes and implementation.

Involving in Form & Fields customizations

Involving for Business rules and script changes and implementation

Involving in Solutions Import and Export.

Involving in script deprecations towards earlier versions.

Involving in document preparations and Development towards new Client Requests.

Client Location: Microsoft Aug2018 to March 2019

HP Sales

Description: HP was an American multinational information technology company headquartered in Palo Alto, California. It developed and provided a wide variety of hardware components as well as software and related services to consumers, small- and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) and large enterprises, including customers in the government, health and education sectors.

Responsibilities:

- Upgraded the USD 2.1 to USD 4.0.
- Worked on Genesys and Logmeln Integrations.
- Worked on Plugins and JavaScript.
- Worked on editable grids.

Environment: Dynamics365, Visual Studio .NET 2017, .NET Framework 4.6, C#.NET, XRM JavaScript, Ribbon Workbench.

Bosch as Senior Software Engineer

Aug 2018 to Till Date

I am the Dynamics365 CRM Technical Consultant with 3 years of experience. I have Good Knowledge in Dynamic365 Sales, Field Service and Power Apps.

TechAspect Solutions as Software Engineer

Nov 2014 to Jun 2018

Techaspect CRM

Description: Techaspect is an innovative digital transformation agency, specializing in delivering digital experience, commerce, and marketing solutions.

For nearly two decades, we have been helping traditional businesses transform and create dynamic digital cultures through disruptive strategies and agile deployment of innovative solutions.

Responsibilities:

Developed plugins and custom workflow activities consuming MS Dynamics CRM web services and using CRM SDK APIs

Integrated the MS CRM Forms with Word press.

Designed the bid qualification form along with the response of approvers team.

Implemented Automated Document Generation of SOW Process.

Created Dashboards, Custom Views.

Implemented the XRM JavaScript for Validations.

Worked on Distribution rules, Security roles, Ribbon workbench, Field Security Profile, hierarchy Security Management, Campaigns.

Environment: Dynamics365, Visual Studio .NET 2017, .NET Framework 4.6, C#.NET, XRM JavaScript, Ribbon Workbench.

Capella Academics August2017 to November 2017

Dynamic CRM Consultant

Capella is an accredited online university dedicated to providing an exceptional, professionally-aligned education that puts you in the best position to succeed in your field. Our challenging curriculum is competency-based, combining foundational

theory with real-world application, to ensure our students receive a high-quality education. Responsibilities:

Configured the Dynamic crm 2016 on-premises, Email Router for the client environment. Created Users and Teams along with Roles.

Implement the Plugin for Distribution rules.

Implemented the XRM JavaScript for Validations.

Designed a Custom workflows for Tasks, Email Triggering and update the records.

Created Dashboards, Custom Views.

Built CRM forms, screens, and views as well as workflows and reports for the user interface.

Worked on Campaigns.

Import and export the Package into Dynamics365.

Environment: DynamicCRM2016, Dynamics365,C#.Net,Plugin Registration Tool.

Honeywell, USA May2016 to December 2016

Content Analyst Project: Honeywell

Honeywell creates technologies that improve quality of life for people around the globe - generating clean energy, increasing our safety and security; enabling people to connect, and collaborate; and equipping our customers with technologies that enable higher productivity. The engineering teams are critical contributors to Honeywell's leading-edge technologies that serve many industries, such as homes and buildings, aviation, defense and space, oil and gas, and chemicals. More than 22,000 engineers work on all aspects of Honeywell's products to tackle some of the world's toughest challenges. From product conception, to technology development and insertion, design, engineering and all the way to delivery, Honeywell's engineering organization makes the world safer, more effective, more comfortable and more productive.

Responsibilities:

Created and added content for the Overview Tabs for all the products. Created and added content for the Specs Tabs for all the products Added new fields for the specs template Added facets for all the products. Worked on renaming the temporary image files. Created and updated tickets in Mantis. Attended the weekly status calls and updated the status accordingly

Environment: Sitecore7.5

Techaspect November2015 - April 2017 Sitecore Developer

Techaspect

Techaspect is an innovative digital transformation agency, specializing in delivering digital experience, commerce, and marketing solutions. For nearly two decades, we have been helping traditional businesses transform and create dynamic digital cultures through disruptive strategies and agile deployment of innovative solutions.

Responsibilities:

Created the new templates.

Migrated the site from Sitecore 8 to Sitecore 8.1 upgrade3 in azure environment. Generated the Email for every 24 hours, which includes WFFM form submiss

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electrical) from Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University (JNTU) in 2013

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
ASP.Net MVC		2019	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
JavaScript		2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=8a2c80142485fb02b27e468f7adfed030a0e09574e1a5d440a1546515c...

SSIS		2020	0 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
Azure DevOps		2020	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
POWER Apps		2020	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
SITECORE	8.2	2018	2 Year(s) 8 Month(s)
SALESFORCE CRM		2018	0 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
MS Dynamics CRM		2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
JQUERY		2019	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Telugu				

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time